2731 SW 74th Street

Oklahoma City, Oklahoma 73159

DawnRNorton@cox.net

(580) 465- 2354

September 9, 2013

Sir or Madam:

I am writing to inquire about a position with VI Marketing and Branding. I have vast experience with media, including sales, marketing and administrative office expertise. I am open to any position offered. I can be a great asset to your agency.

I graduated from the University of Oklahoma in May 2012 with a Bachelor of Arts in both sociology and communication. My time with the University of Oklahoma included involvement with many leadership opportunities and participation with organizations that allowed me to hone my communication skills. I served as the chair of the Problems and Projects Committee within Student Congress. As Problems and Projects Chair, I was responsible for supervising congress projects on campus that did not deal directly with academic policies. I competed for the University of Oklahoma Sooner Speech Team in both parliamentary debate and extemporaneous speaking. I organized my senior sociology capstone final group project which looked in to real causes of child obesity for Cleveland County using the SPSS statistical program and offered policies to be enacted. My results were presented to the Cleveland County Health Department. I also have seen the direct results of behind the scenes duties with my time employed with Noble Energy, Camp Classen, and Lindmark (now Stellar) Outdoor Advertising.

After graduation, I went on to work for Clear Channel Media + Entertainment as the Key Account Coordinator and was responsible for roughly \$3.5 million split between four account executives. Since I became the Key Account Coordinator, my combined Account Executive new revenue has increased in excess of \$100,000. I have dealt with some of the largest accounts that advertise with Clear Channel. My duties include: order input, traffic instruction, maintaining files, designing digital banners among other duties. During my time with Clear Channel, I have discovered a deep love of Media, and would love the opportunity to further my career with your company.

I would welcome the opportunity to meet with you to discuss the position and my qualifications in more detail. I hope to hear from you soon. If you have any questions, please do not hesitate to e-mail me at DawnRNorton@cox.net or contact me at 580-465-2354.

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Dawn Norton

2731 SW 74th St. Oklahoma City, OK 73159

T:580-465-2354 E: DawnRNorton@cox.net

EXPERIENCE

Key Account Coordinator, Clear Channel Media + Entertainment

Oklahoma City, OK — 2012-Present

My duties currently include supporting four Senior Account Executives and helping them maximize revenue opportunities by assisting with administrative tasks such as order entry and management, collection of payment, setting appointments with clients, and facilitating internal communications. I also assist with the preparation of sales proposals, perform research and support key sales and promotional events. I also contact clients and manage customer service. I am responsible for roughly \$3.5 million in account revenue. I work under strict deadlines and intense pressure to ensure that my Account Executives perform to their greatest potential. Furthermore, I perform collection calls for house accounts and design digital banners for clients using Photoshop. Notable accounts that I have worked on include: Prodigal, LLC, 7-Eleven, Frontier Auto Group, David Stanley Dodge, the Oklahoma City Zoo, Bob Moore Auto Group, Reynolds Ford, and many more not listed here.

Accomplishments

- An increase of new revenue in excess of \$100,000 over the past year.
- I am part of a successful weekly segment that airs during the afternoon drive slot on KTOK.
- I have been given the opportunity to take the lead on various accounts.

Staff Specialist, Lindmark Outdoor Advertising

Purcell, Oklahoma — 2009-2010

My duties included reviewing 650 billboard leases to ensure that they were not detrimental to the company and inputting the information of said leases into Lindmark's computer system for easy access. If a lease was found to be lacking, it was my job to bring it to the attention of the leasing manager for renegotiation. Later on I would do minor maintenance on billboards, such as managing electricity bills..

Accomplishments

- Streamlined the Leasing Database.
- Received firsthand experience in customer service in media.

Office Assistant, Camp Classen

Davis, Oklahoma — 2008

My duties included maintaining client database, ensuring payment for campers, aiding with check-in and check-out processes, filing paperwork, fielding parent calls, providing customer service, and other tasks as needed.

Accounts Receivable Summer Intern, Noble Energy

Ardmore, OK — 2005-2007

My duties included applying deposits daily, making multi-million dollar collection calls, routine filing, maintaining excel worksheets with monthly payment data, working with other departments to maintain cohesiveness, doing account maintenance, and other duties as needed. I also aided in Accounts Payable, the Mail Department, and at the reception desk.

EDUCATION

University Of Oklahoma- Bachelor of Arts

Dual Major in Communication and Sociology

Norman, Oklahoma — 2007-2012

- Elected Student Congress Representative, Humanities District for 2 Terms
- Problems and Projects Committee Chair
- Sooner Speech Team Vice President
- 4th Place Lincoln-Douglas Debate- Oklahoma Intercollegiate Tournament
- 3rd Place Parliamentary Debate- Oklahoma Intercollegiate Tournament
- 10th Place JV Parliamentary Debate- Pi Kappa Delta National Tournament
- Sociology Student Advisory Committee
- Reviewed University of Oklahoma Sociology Journal

Lone Grove High School

High School Diploma

Lone Grove, Oklahoma — 2003-2007

REFERENCES

Kathy Jones Senior Account Executive Clear Channel Media + Entertainment 405-613-6424

David Workman Senior Account Manager Clear Channel Media + Entertainment 405-630-4196

Clayton Dodds Consultant- Legal Marketing Nolo Press 618-334-0952